https://sleezybarbhorsewear.com/privacy-policy/

Skip to content
Privacy Policy
Home » Privacy Policy
Privacy Policydrakebarb2016-12-24T08:31:08-05:00
Privacy PolicyShopping at Sleezy Barb Horsewear is always safe and secure.
At SleezyBarbHorsewear.com your right to privacy and data security is a primary concern. All information you provide to us is strictly confidential. We do not and will not share any of your information with any other parties; i.e. sell your name to a mailing list. Because of our commitment to our users’ privacy, we are disclosing our information practices.
Ordering:
We request information from the user on our order form. A user must provide contact information (such as name, email, and shipping address) and financial information (such as credit card number, expiration date).
This information issued for billing purposes only and to fill customer’s orders. If we have trouble processing an order, the information is used to contact the user.
Third Party Intermediaries:
We use an outside shipping company to ship orders, and an outside company to process credit card transactions. These companies do not retain, share, store or use personally identifiable information for any secondary purposes. Information between the servers is encrypted.
Surveys and Contests:
From time-to-time our site request information from users via surveys or contests. Participation in these surveys or contests is completely voluntary and the user therefore has a choice whether or not to disclose this information. The requested information typically includes contact information (such as name and shipping address), and demographic information (such as zip code). Contact information will be used to notify the winners and award prizes. Survey information will be used for purposes of monitoring or improving the use and satisfaction of this site. Users’ personally identifiable information is not shared with any third parties.
Customer Confidentiality:
Sleezy Barb Horsewear does not share, sell, or trade information about our customers. All information provided by you to us is strictly confidential. We never have and never will make mailing lists or any information about our customers available to any agency or company for marketing or commercial purposes.
Spamming, Pop-ups, and eMail Policy:
Sleezy Barb Horsewear does not spam, solicit by telephone, send unsolicited emails, nor put pop-up messages onto your computer. Any email sent will be only to acknowledge information on orders received, or to to notify customers of when their order is shipped.
Cookies:
A cookie is a small data file that is stored by your Web browser on your ocmputer. Cookies enable you to place an order on our Web site. They also allow us to enhance and personalize your online shopping experience, so that the information you receive is more relevant to you. We use cookies to remember what items are in your shoping cart and recognize you when you return to our Web site.
Secure Sockets Layer (SSL):
We use Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) encryption to encrypt your transactions. SSL encrypts all of your personal information, including credit card number, name, and address, so that it cannot be read as the information travels over the Internet.
Privacy of Children on Our Web Site:
Our Web site is not intended for use by children under the age of 13, and we do not knowingly collect personal information from children under the age of 13.
Option to Call in Your Credit Card Number:
If you do not want to supply your credit card information over the Internet, you can always call us at (989-227-5741) to place your order.
MENUMENU
Horse SleezysFull Body SleezysHorse Body SuitsPony & Small Horse WearMiniature Horse WearShoulder GuardsFor Beautiful ManesFor Luxurious TailsLeg Wraps & Sport Boot CoversHelmet Covers & Helmet BagsSaddle CoversHi Viz Horse WearBit WarmersGiftsHorse Costumes & Ideas
Costumes For HorsesHorse Costume Design IdeasCustomer's Horse CostumesFast & Easy Horse Costumes
Sizing and Colors
SizingColors
Ready Made - ON SALESale Barn, Specials & DealsFan Page
